Dylan Larrivee

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A high-performance, self-starting full-stack developer with two years of experience building out custom solution SaaS applications in the marketing technology space. Solutions-driven with a strong passion for technology and always looking for opportunities to grow as a developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Shaw Scott Aug. 2018 – Present

Technical Services Consultant

Remote

- Designed and manage company AWS infrastructure following the well architecture principles.
- Built and maintain multiple highly scalable web-based SaaS application products.
- Improved client's retargeting email content by developing JavaScript code for use in Google Tag Manager.
- Architect and implement highly dynamic preference center forms for multiple clients using JavaScript and Vue.js framework that allowed marketers to gain more insight on their customer's preferences.
- Manage the technical delivery of ESP onboarding, data integrations, and migration elements of a marketing cloud implementation.
- Lead hands-on, expert-level technical training assistance to the client and internal services team.

Lister Digital

Apr. 2017 – Aug. 2018

Remote

Senior Campaign Specialist

- The US technical lead for 3 accounts simultaneously and coordinated efforts between onshore and offshore efforts.
- Designed data model solutions and provided best practices recommendations based on clients' marketing strategies and requirements.
- Increased client's email conversion using an automated campaign building tool I developed.

Oracle Feb. 2015 – Mar. 2017

Expert Services Associate

Seattle, WA

- Scoped, built and designed brand new event-triggered campaigns for clients on time, on budget, and error-free using the Oracle Responsys Interact marketing platform.
- Consult clients on technical and complex projects while also improving efficiency in business requirements and processes.

PROFFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

- Curbside Notification App (2020): MERN stack App hosted on AWS. A Web based SaaS application that I designed, coded and deployed that allows retail brands to easily manage their curbside customer experience. Currently in beta testing before going live as a company product.
- Forms Builder App (2019): Vue.js, Node.js, PostgreSQL hosted on AWS. Onboarded new clients onto the application and built out custom features and upgrades on the existing application.
- Oracle Responsys API Integration Apps (2019): Node.js, PostgreSQL, Vue.js, AWS, Python. Built multiple
 applications and POCs that work on top of the Responsys API to provide additional functionality not available in the
 platform.
- Work daily with a range of web-related technologies including HTML, CSS, Vue, JavaScript, Node.js, RESTful APIs, JSON, XML as well as dynamic programming languages including Freemarker and Python.
- SQL within the Oracle Responsys marketing software and in the PostgreSQL RDS environment.
- Building and maintaining web applications and ETL processes in the AWS environment using S3, EC2, ECS with Docker containers, ELB, RDS (PostgreSQL), DocumentDB, Elastic Beanstalk, CloudWatch and Route 53.
- Version control using Git.
- Software development methodologies such as TDD, CI/CD, AGILE/SCRUM.

EDUCATION